Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine Records UA041
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files, 1969 -- 1986; 1978 -- 1984; UA041.003; 3.6 Linear Feet
  - Patent policy, 1978; UA041.003.005.00020 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Academic advisory committee, 1977; UA041.003.005.00021 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Imperial Medical Center of Iran (Quinnipiac College), 1978; UA041.003.005.00022 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Animal medical center, 1978; UA041.003.005.00023 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Nutrition center, n.d., UA041.003.005.00024 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Veterinary medical manpower needs, 1978; UA041.003.005.00025 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1978; UA041.003.005.00026 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Report to the president, 1978; UA041.003.005.00027 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Biohazards reference material, 1974 -- 1978; UA041.003.005.00028 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Recruitment: faculty, 1977; UA041.003.005.00029 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Regional resources (faculty), 1978; UA041.003.005.00030 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Recruitment - administrators, 1978; UA041.003.005.00031 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Curriculum, 1981; UA041.003.005.00032 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Library, 1981; UA041.003.005.00033 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - AVMA: admissions and student affairs, 1983; UA041.003.005.00034 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Department of surgery - small animal, 1981; UA041.003.005.00035 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Basic science, 1981; UA041.003.005.00036 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - AVMA - Large animal clinical, 1981; UA041.003.005.00037 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Transcript, 1979; UA041.003.005.00038 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Visiting committee, April 7 visit, 1980 -- 1981; UA041.003.005.00039 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Clinical sciences, 1981; UA041.003.005.00040 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Cornell University, 1977 -- 1979; UA041.003.005.00041 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Veterinary School, Tuskegee Institute site visit, 1972 -- 1978; UA041.003.005.00042 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Site visit information, 1978; UA041.003.005.00043 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - School of Veterinary Medicine, 1977 -- 1979; UA041.003.005.00044 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Land grant task force, 1977 -- 1979; UA041.003.005.00045 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Land grant universities (national association), 1977; UA041.003.005.00046 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Land grant universities (task force meeting, 1-31-78), 1978; UA041.003.005.00047 (Box UA041 Shared 1)
  - Land grant universities (model compact), UA041.003.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Legislation (Federal), HEW bills & acts, 1976 -- 1978; UA041.003.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Library - donations, 1976 -- 1978; UA041.003.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Maine Poultry Federation, 1978; UA041.003.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - U.S. veterinary medical manpower, 1976 -- 1978; UA041.003.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Masachusetts Board of Registration in Veterinary Medicine, 1977 -- 1978; UA041.003.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Mass. Farm Bureau mtg., 1979; UA041.003.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - UMass., general, 1977 -- 1980; UA041.003.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - N.E, Governors' conference (meetings), 1976 -- 1979; UA041.003.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - New England Regional Commission (NERCOM), 1977 -- 1979; UA041.003.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - NERCOM / Tufts contract I, 1977 -- 1978; UA041.003.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - MSPCA - ARL, 1979; UA041.003.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Veterinary School: meeting minutes & votes, 1976 -- 1977; UA041.003.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Veterinary School, model compact for vet. med. education, 1977; UA041.003.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Contract II - NERCOM - Tufts, 1977; UA041.003.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Contract II - NERCOM - Tufts, 1977 -- 1978; UA041.003.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - N.E. research - primate research centers, 1976 -- 1977; UA041.003.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - University of Pennsylvania - general vet school, 1976 -- 1977; UA041.003.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - University of Pennsylvania - New Bolton Center Vet. School, 1978; UA041.003.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - University of Pennsylvania Dean Marshak corres., 1976 -- 1978; UA041.003.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - President's report - School of Veterinary Medicine, 1978; UA041.003.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Status report, 1979; UA041.003.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - Progress report, 1978; UA041.003.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - 1976 (progress reports), UA041.003.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - Progress reports, 1976 -- 1978; UA041.003.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - Quarterly report, 1977; UA041.003.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - Regional school, 1979; UA041.003.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - Renovations 1978-79, UA041.003.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - Resources - Wein memos, 1979; UA041.003.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - Resources - PR, 1979; UA041.003.006.00030 (Box 6)
  - Resources - PR: news releases, 1978 -- 1979; UA041.003.006.00031 (Box 6)
  - Resources - PR: Tufts news, 1978; UA041.003.006.00032 (Box 6)
  - Resources - PR: at Tufts, 1978 -- 1979; UA041.003.006.00033 (Box 6)
  - Resources - PR: descriptions of Veterinary School, n.d., UA041.003.006.00034 (Box 6)
  - Resources - PR: UPNE, 1979; UA041.003.006.00035 (Box 6)
  - Resources - PR: WBZ editorials, n.d., UA041.003.006.00036 (Box 6)
  - States - Mass.: FY 1983 budget, 1981; UA041.003.006.00037 (Box 6)
  - State - Mass.: FY 1982 budget, 1980 -- 1981; UA041.003.006.00038 (Box 6)
  - States - Mass.: FY 1981 budget, 1979 -- 1981; UA041.003.006.00039 (Box 6)
  - States - Mass.: FY 1980 budget, 1978 -- 1979; UA041.003.006.00040 (Box 6)
  - States - New Jersey, 1978 -- 1979; UA041.003.006.00041 (Box 6)
  - States - New Jersey, 1978 -- 1979; UA041.003.006.00042 (Box 6)
  - States - Vermont, 1978; UA041.003.006.00043 (Box 6)
  - Veterinary School - health insurance, 1969 -- 1977; UA041.003.006.00044 (Box 6)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, n.d., UA041.003.006.00045 (Box 6)
  - Talbot correspondence, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1977; UA041.003.006.00046 (Box 6)
  - Trustees, 1977 -- 1979; UA041.003.006.00047 (Box 6)
  - Trustees: executive committee, 1979; UA041.003.006.00048 (Box 6)
  - Frankie Leoff (1), 1976 -- 1977; UA041.003.006.00049 (Box 6)
  - Frankie Leoff (2), 1976 -- 1977; UA041.003.006.00050 (Box 6)
  - Angell Memorial Hospital, 1978; UA041.003.006.00051 (Box 6)
  - Legislation - New England states, 1978; UA041.003.006.00052 (Box 6)
  - Tufts financial: dean's budget FY '79, 1978; UA041.003.006.00053 (Box 6)
  - Tufts financial: grants, contract 1978-79, UA041.003.006.00054 (Box 6)
  - Tufts Grafton plans, 1977; UA041.003.006.00055 (Box 6)
  - U.S.D.A., 1978; UA041.003.006.00056 (Box 6)
  - U.S.D.A.: FHA, 1978; UA041.003.006.00057 (Box 6)
  - U.S.D.A.: animal health & disease research funds, 1978; UA041.003.006.00058 (Box 6)
  - Veterinary School - Endowed chair in animal behavior, 1980; UA041.003.006.00059 (Box 6)
  - Veterinary School for New England - feasibility study, 1976; UA041.003.006.00060 (Box 6)
  - Veterinary School - research survey, 1977; UA041.003.006.00061 (Box 6)
  - Veterinary resources - capital campaign, 1979; UA041.003.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Veterinary resources, development program, 1979 -- 1980; UA041.003.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Veterinary School resources - publications, 1979; UA041.003.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Veterinary School - annual report, 1978 -- 1979; UA041.003.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Tufts University School of Veterinary Medicine Bylaws, n.d., UA041.003.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Accreditation, 1977 -- 1986; UA041.003.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - Accreditation, 1983 -- 1985; UA041.003.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Accreditation, 1981 -- 1983; UA041.003.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - Accreditation, 1979; UA041.003.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - Animal welfare committee, 1983 -- 1984; UA041.003.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Annual report, 1981 -- 1982; UA041.003.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - AVMA, 1981 -- 1982; UA041.003.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - Basic research - grants, reports, 1981 -- 1982; UA041.003.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - Basic sciences, 1981 -- 1982; UA041.003.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - Basic science, 1983 -- 1984; UA041.003.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - Cancer Center - core grant progress report, 1984; UA041.003.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - Continuing education, 1982 -- 1983; UA041.003.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - Curriculum, 1986; UA041.003.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - Curriculum, 1984 -- 1986; UA041.003.007.00019 (Box 7)
  - Vet course evaluation (info), 1984; UA041.003.007.00020 (Box 7)
  - Curriculum - clinical, 1982 -- 1986; UA041.003.007.00021 (Box 7)
  - Curriculum committee, 1980 -- 1983; UA041.003.007.00022 (Box 7)
  - Curriculum committee, 1983; UA041.003.007.00023 (Box 7)
  - Curriculum committee, 1983 -- 1984; UA041.003.007.00024 (Box 7)
  - Curriculum requests, 1984; UA041.003.007.00025 (Box 7)
  - Curriculum - vet, 1979 -- 1981; UA041.003.007.00026 (Box 7)
  - Dept. reviews, 1982; UA041.003.007.00027 (Box 7)
  - Diagnostic lab, 1981 -- 1985; UA041.003.007.00028 (Box 7)
  - Education com., advanced, 1982 -- 1984; UA041.003.007.00029 (Box 7)
  - Educational media, 1981 -- 1983; UA041.003.007.00030 (Box 7)
  - Elective program, 1982 -- 1985; UA041.003.007.00031 (Box 7)
  - Environmental studies, 1983; UA041.003.007.00032 (Box 7)
  - External rotation committee, 1983; UA041.003.007.00033 (Box 7)
  - Facilities, 1983; UA041.003.007.00034 (Box 7)
  - Faculty appointments, 1982 -- 1983; UA041.003.007.00035 (Box 7)
  - Angell Memorial, 1984; UA041.003.007.00036 (Box 7)
  - Angell Memorial, 1984; UA041.003.007.00037 (Box 7)
  - Angell Memorial, 1984; UA041.003.007.00038 (Box 7)
  - Angell Memorial, 1984; UA041.003.007.00039 (Box 7)
  - Angell [1 of 2], 1983 -- 1985; UA041.003.007.00040 (Box 7)
  - Angell [2 of 2], 1983; UA041.003.007.00041 (Box 7)
  - Angell agreement [1 of 3], 1983; UA041.003.007.00042 (Box 7)
  - Angell agreement [2 of 3], 1982 -- 1983; UA041.003.007.00043 (Box 7)
  - Angell agreement [3 of 3], 1982; UA041.003.007.00044 (Box 7)
- Programs and events, 1979 -- 1995; UA041.004; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains clippings, programs, scripts and other materials pertaining to special events, including commencement, grand openings of buildings, and Equifest, held at the Tufts University School of Veterinary Medicine. These materials date from 1979 to 1995. Many of these materials were in boxes received prior to 1997 and the original order of the files cannot be assured.
  This series is arranged as found, primarily by subject.
  - Commencement program - 2nd commencement, 1984; UA041.004.008.00001 (Box UA041 Shared 2)
  - Opening of Franklin M. Loew building, 1993; UA041.004.008.00002 (Box UA041 Shared 2)
  - Large animal hospital, grand opening, 1982; UA041.004.008.00003 (Box UA041 Shared 2)
  - Commencement script, 1994; UA041.004.008.00004 (Box UA041 Shared 2)
  - Commencement script, 1995; UA041.004.008.00005 (Box UA041 Shared 2)
  - Programs, 1980 -- 1995; UA041.004.008.00006 (Box UA041 Shared 2)
  - Commencement, 1983; UA041.004.008.00007 (Box UA041 Shared 2)
  - 3rd graduation, 1985; UA041.004.008.00008 (Box UA041 Shared 2)
  - Commencement, 1986; UA041.004.008.00009 (Box UA041 Shared 2)
  - 2nd graduation, 1984; UA041.004.008.00010 (Box UA041 Shared 2)
  - Pritchard, William Roy - citation for honorary degree, n.d., UA041.004.008.00011 (Box UA041 Shared 2)
  - Veterinary M Club dinner, 1987; UA041.004.008.00012 (Box UA041 Shared 2)
  - Opening of TUSVM, press kit, 1979; UA041.004.008.00013 (Box UA041 Shared 2)
  - Veterinary School Equifest, 1983; UA041.004.008.00014 (Box UA041 Shared 2)
  - Veterinary School, Equifest, 1984; UA041.004.008.00015 (Box UA041 Shared 2)
  - Amelia Peabody Pavillion, dedication, 1981; UA041.004.008.00016 (Box UA041 Shared 2)
- Executive faculty board minutes, 1985 -- 1988; UA041.005; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains minutes of the executive board of the faculty of the School of Veterinary Medicine, from 1985 to 1988.
  - Executive faculty board minutes, 1985 -- 1988; UA041.005.008.00017 (Box UA041 Shared 2)
- Newspaper clippings and publicity materials, 1975 -- 1994; 1976 -- 1980; UA041.006; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series consists primarily of newspaper clippings about the Tufts University School of Veterinary Medicine, including its planning and development. Also includes press releases about TUSVM. Most materials date between 1976 and 1984, although there are some newspaper clippings from the early 1990s. Many of the clippings were originally housed in vinyl binders and were rehoused in processing with the original order maintained.
  - Clippings, Jan-June, 1991; UA041.006.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Clippings, 1976 -- 1979; UA041.006.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Vet binder 1, 1976 -- 1977; UA041.006.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Vet binder 1 - news stories, 1977 -- 1978; UA041.006.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Vet binder 1 - news stories, 1977; UA041.006.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Vet binder 1 - news stories, 1977; UA041.006.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Vet binder 1 - news stories, 1976 -- 1977; UA041.006.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Vet binder 1 - news stories, 1976; UA041.006.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Vet School binder 2, 1979 -- 1980; UA041.006.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Vet School binder 2, 1979; UA041.006.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1977 -- 1984; UA041.006.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1976 -- 1990; UA041.006.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Vet School, 1975 -- 1978; UA041.006.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1977 -- 1984; UA041.006.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1984; UA041.006.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - Veterinary School, faculty and staff, 1984; UA041.006.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Veterinary School, Niger Integrated Livestock Production Project: newsletter, 1982 -- 1984; UA041.006.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1978 -- 1994; UA041.006.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - Press release, 1983; UA041.006.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - Press releases, 1980 -- 1984; UA041.006.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - Brochures and pamphlets, 1978; UA041.006.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Brochures and pamphlets, 1980 -- 1988; UA041.006.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - Press releases and clipping, small animal hospital, 1981 -- 1984; UA041.006.009.00023 (Box 9)
- Masters theses, 1996 -- 2016; UA041.007; 41 Digital Object(s); 388 Megabytes
  This series/sub-series is open for research.
  This series was minimally arranged.
  Theses submitted for the MS in Animals and Public Policy degree.
  - Inviting Politics to Dinner: An Ecofeminist Analysis of Meat Eating, 2001-02; UA041.007.00001; Abromaitis, Susanne; 1 Digital Object(s); 51.5 Megabytes
    Thesis submitted for the MS in Animals and Public Policy degree.
    Veterinary medicine -- Study and teaching; Center for Animals and Public Policy; Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine
  - Dehorning Practices and Perceptions of Southern New England Dairy Farmers, 2009-08-21; UA041.007.00002; Bannon, Kerry; 1 Digital Object(s); 395 Kilobytes
  - Creating Long-Term Change in International Animal Welfare: An Argument for Engaging Youth in Participatory Inquiry Using Photography, 2015-04-28; UA041.007.00003; Beberman, Brianna; 1 Digital Object(s); 922 Kilobytes
  - Exploring Contemporary Thoughts on the Use of Environmental Enrichment Programs in 'No-Kill' Animal Shelters, 2008-08-15; UA041.007.00004; Castillo, Roberto; 1 Digital Object(s); 299 Kilobytes
  - Exam Induced Stress Levels of First and Second Year Veterinary Medicine Students, circa 2013; UA041.007.00005; Ciaramello, Taralyn M.; Lindsay, Anne; Byrnes, John J.; 1 Digital Object(s); 471 Kilobytes
  - Animal Adoption and the Pet Acquisition Process, circa 2006; UA041.007.00006; Conklin, Bryn; 1 Digital Object(s); 878 Kilobytes
  - To Declaw or Not To Declaw, That is the Question: Behavior and Declaw Status of Cats in Suburban Massachusetts, 2001-04; UA041.007.00007; Connolly, Kelly Elizabeth; 1 Digital Object(s); 30 Megabytes
  - African Elephant (Loxodonta africana) Management Policy, 1997-12-03; UA041.007.00008; de Liedekerke, Valerie; 1 Digital Object(s); 115 Megabytes
  - Clarifying the Dairy Welfare Audit, circa 2011; UA041.007.00009; Doyle, Kristina; McMullen, Brendan; 1 Digital Object(s); 192 Kilobytes
  - The Effects of Training Attitudes Toward the Horse on Training Methods in Three Disciplines, 2004-08; UA041.007.00010; Dufresne, Lisa; 1 Digital Object(s); 29.1 Megabytes
  - Evaluation of Enrichment for Reptiles in Zoos, 2015-12-18; UA041.007.00011; Eagan, Taylor; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.34 Megabytes
  - Effects of an Extended-Use ThunderShirt Pressure-Wrap Protocol on Chronic Stress in Shelter Dogs, 2016-12-15; UA041.007.00012; Epstein, Jody; 1 Digital Object(s); 259 Kilobytes
  - The Feral Cat Controversy: An Interpretive Policy Analysis in Support of TNR, 2016; UA041.007.00013; Evans, Elizabeth; 1 Digital Object(s); 672 Kilobytes
  - Biscayne National Park's Loggerhead Turtle Conservation Program in South Florida: An Analysis, 2011-01; UA041.007.00014; Garcia, Tamara; 1 Digital Object(s); 808 Kilobytes
  - The Whale Shark Tourism Industry in Holbox, Mexico, 2013-01-02; UA041.007.00015; Getty, Susan; 1 Digital Object(s); 15.2 Megabytes
  - Bridging the Gap: Educating decision makers about the connections between human violence and animal cruelty, circa 2010; UA041.007.00016; Grace, Martha; Grande, Lorna; 1 Digital Object(s); 211 Kilobytes
  - Wildlife Contraception: An Evaluation of Options, Ethical Considerations, and Public Attitudes, 1996-07-31; UA041.007.00017; Huebner, Linda; 1 Digital Object(s); 40.5 Megabytes
  - Use of accelerometers ti measure tress levels in shelter dogs, 2010-08-20; UA041.007.00018; Jones, Sarah; 1 Digital Object(s); 489 Kilobytes
  - Animals in Elderly and Assisted Living Housing: Policies and Attitudes, 2007-08-15; UA041.007.00019; Kaigler, Elizabeth B.; 1 Digital Object(s); 262 Kilobytes
  - Effects of Direct Human Interactions with Captive Tigers on Perceptions of Tiger Conservation Status, 2013-12-17; UA041.007.00020; Koss, Claire; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.99 Megabytes
  - Recovery Diary Survey: Exploring Caretaker Practices and Cat Behavior after Trap-Neuter-Return (TNR), circa 2015; UA041.007.00021; Kowalski, Amanda; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.28 Megabytes
  - Turtle Road Mortality in Grafton, Massachusetts, 2006-08-31; UA041.007.00022; Lackner, Corinne I.; 1 Digital Object(s); 969 Kilobytes
  - Justification for Community Medicine and Low-Price Veterinary Clinics in Underserved Areas, 2015; UA041.007.00023; Lavallee, Elizabeth; 1 Digital Object(s); 586 Kilobytes
  - What about fish? Why Some "Vegetarians" Eat Seafood and Implications for the Vegetarian Movement, circa 2012; UA041.007.00024; McPherson, Kate D.; 1 Digital Object(s); 168 Kilobytes
  - Killing for Conservation: A Petition to Downlist Namibian Cheetahs (Acinonyx jubatus) under the Endangered Species Act to Allow the Importation of Sport-hunted Trophies, 2000-02; UA041.007.00025; Miller, Crystal D.; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.2 Megabytes
  - The Impact of Assistance Dogs on Their Owners, 1997-06; UA041.007.00026; Moore, Diane V.; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.4 Megabytes
  - Text for Farm Animal Welfare An Interactive CD-ROM Tutorial, 1996; UA041.007.00027; O'Driscoll, Jennifer; 1 Digital Object(s); 31 Megabytes
  - Volunteer Participation with Non-Lethal Alternatives in US Wildlife Management, 2014-12-19; UA041.007.00028; Oriol-Morway, Danika; 1 Digital Object(s); 212 Kilobytes
  - Biomedical scientists' recognition and alleviation of pain and distress in laboratory rats and mice, circa 2002; UA041.007.00029; Parkison, Valerie; Rutberg, Allen; Dizard, Jan E.; 1 Digital Object(s); 420 Kilobytes
  - Allegory of Want: Coyotes, Conflict, and Animal Control Officers in Massachusetts, 2008; UA041.007.00030; Pellegrini, Nadine; 1 Digital Object(s); 341 Kilobytes
  - Models for a Voluntary Accreditation System for Companion Animal Shelters, 2013-11-24; UA041.007.00031; Pesek, Julia; McCobb, Emily; 1 Digital Object(s); 68 Kilobytes
  - Humane Endpoints: The current state of affairs of animal use in infectious disease research, 2006-12-01; UA041.007.00032; Picard, Michele Denise; 1 Digital Object(s); 468 Kilobytes
  - Assessing Student Attitudes on Farm Animal Welfare at a Veterinary College, circa 2014; UA041.007.00033; Popescu, Jessica N.; McMullen, Brendan; 1 Digital Object(s); 262 Kilobytes
  - Intersecting Social Movements: LGBTQ Rights and Animal Rights, 2012-12-25; UA041.007.00034; Rothstein, Melissa; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.04 Megabytes
  - An analysis of bacterial antibiotic resistance in a small animal veterinary clinic, 1999; UA041.007.00035; Sabet, Nevin; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.1 Megabytes
  - Applying the Court Appointed Special Advocate Model to Dogs in the Legal System, 2007-08-15; UA041.007.00036; Silverstein, Rebecca; 1 Digital Object(s); 388 Kilobytes
  - Effectiveness of Water-flow Devices as Beaver Conflict Resolution Tools: A satisfaction survey of Massachusetts clients, 2006-08-28; UA041.007.00037; Spock, Mary; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.39 Megabytes
  - Connecting Knowledge Levels of Owners with Pet Rabbit Welfare, circa 2013; UA041.007.00038; Vancelette, Ellen; 1 Digital Object(s); 184 Kilobytes
  - Gillnets and Conservation of the Franciscana Dolphin (Pontoporia blainvillei) in Argentina: a policy perspective, 2002; UA041.007.00039; Weiskel, Heidi W.; Bordino, Pablo; Arias, Alejandro M.; 1 Digital Object(s); 183 Kilobytes
  - Interpretive Analysis of Stakeholder Response the U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service's Proposed Removal Experiments of Barred Owls in the Endangered Northern Spotted Owl's Habitat Range, 2011-08; UA041.007.00040; Wilson, Stefanie L.; 1 Digital Object(s); 294 Kilobytes
  - Disposable Pets: Exploration into the Relinquishment of Unwanted Reptiles, 2007-08-15; UA041.007.00041; Wittman, Emily; 1 Digital Object(s); 342 Kilobytes
- Additional accessions, UA041.000405
  - Pamphlets, newsletters, CD-ROM, 1978 -- 1997; UA041-001 (Box data_value_missing_feb8c00ec53b2ecd7c7cbb2c128efa15, Box 1)
  - Program and Predesign Report, Newskit, 1978 -- 1997; UA041-002 (Box data_value_missing_11bc2dbb750c300ff9d1403ef7c99db5, Box 2)
  - Materials collected by Dean Loew and relating to the formation of the TUSVM including the earliest feasibility studies, 1982 -- 1986; UA041-003 (Box data_value_missing_ea2d006a626f21bfcf59a1305149aaba, Box 3)
  - Executive Faculty Board papers, files on the early history of vet school departments, 1981 -- 1994; UA041-004 (Box data_value_missing_07f27cf3461b441088005b78b8b118b6, Box 4)
  - Curriculum; financial reports; Three year plan; other reports, 1979 -- 1988; UA041-005 (Box data_value_missing_4a3c5c2a3261acf65179f9c58d8828a4, Box 5)
  - Accreditation manual; student/dean communications; historical state appropriations; Charles River overflow; Annual reports; Press clippings, 1977 -- 2006; UA041-006 (Box data_value_missing_4a3c5c2a3261acf65179f9c58d8828a4, Box 6)
  - Archival material collected by Dean Loew and relaing to the formation of the Vet School, 1969 -- 1978; UA041-007 (Box data_value_missing_07f27cf3461b441088005b78b8b118b6, Box 7)
  - Archival material collected by Dean Loew and relaing to the formation of the Vet School, 1982 -- 1986; UA041-008 (Box data_value_missing_bf44e70ad8a7ec0abc927c92b7a919f9, Box 8)
  - Dean Loew and President Mayer correspondence and subject files, 1982 -- 1990; UA041-009 (Box data_value_missing_bf44e70ad8a7ec0abc927c92b7a919f9, Box 9)
  - Agnes Varis honorary degree and photos, photos from NORD ceremony, 1999 -- 2003; UA041-010 (Box data_value_missing_e433e7be9b4d85ea289de84f60c6e308, Box 10)
  - Agnes Varis Campus Center dedication poster, 2003; UA041-011 (Box data_value_missing_498791eb98799a80c7fccaa8409ea9a6, Box 11)
  - Oral history videos, 2012; UA041-012
  - Tufts Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine Naming Ceremony May 5, 2005, UA041-013